like I said welcome brothers and sisters
to another Wednesday question and answer
well we open up with the Ten
Commandments that God commanded the
whole world to keep brother tanel and
God spake all these words saying I am
the Lord thy God which have brought thee
out of the land of Egypt out of the
house of bondage thou sh have no other
gods before me thou shall not make unto
thee any Graven image or any likeness of
anything that is in heaven above or that
is in the earth beneath or that is in
the water under the Earth thou shall not
bow down thyself to them nor serve them
why the Lord thy God am a jealous
God thisit SE the iniquity of the
fathers upon the children unto the third
and fourth generation of them that hate
me and show Mercy into thousands of them
that love me and keep my Commandments
thou shall not take the name of the Lord
thy God in vain for the Lord will not
hold him Guiltless that take up his name
in vain remember the Sabbath day to keep
it holy six days shall th do all thy
work but the seventh day is the Sabbath
of the Lord thy God and that thou shall
not do any work thou nor thy son nor th
daughter that man servant nor thaty maid
servant nor th cattle nor that stranger
that is within thy gates for in six days
the Lord made Heaven and Earth the sea
and all that in them is and rested the
seven day wherefore the Lord bless the
Sabbath day and Hol day honor thy father
and thy mother that thy days may be long
upon the the land which the Lord thy God
give thee thou shall not kill thou shall
not commit adultery thou shall not steal
thou shall not bear false witness
against thy neighbor thou shall not
cover thy neighbor's house thou shall
not cover thy neighbor's wife know his
man's servant nor his ma servant nor his
Ox nor his ass nor anything that is thy
neighbors we read Exodus 21 through 17
and may the Lord have a blessing to the
reading of his words in Jesus name we
pray amen
amen so here on question and answer you
can ask us a question and we'll answer
it according to the King James Bible and
if we cannot find the answer we will
seek further counsel to bring you an
answer at a later time the questions we
will not answer are the vague long
scripture questions and the questions of
debate we are not here to debate we are
here to spread to True Gospel of the
Living God so please be direct with your
answers so we can be as direct as
possible be as direct as possible with
your questions so we can be as direct as
possible with our answers out of the
King James Bible no other Bibles or
books will be acknowledged on this
program also keep in mind that this is a
live stream so feel free to send in your
questions that pertain to everlasting
life we just ask that you keep your
questions to a two scripture maximum but
let me introduce to you the family
that's on the panel this evening we got
brother Dre good evening brother
Jerome Grace and peace Brother Julius
good evening everybody brother tanzel
good
evening sister
Deborah brother
Sean and we have a
guest okay you with us Deborah yes all
right good to have you and we have the
guest caller with us and I'm brother
Cornell so sister Deborah start us off
with our first question of the evening
yes there are several heeld over
questions that will be answered first
before getting into tonight's Q&A melan
natural Journey
ask can can women wear pans outside of
church how about makeup and jewelry and
braiding hair all right so answer to
your first question yes women can wear
pants outside of the
church and we are talking about the
Israel of God here located in Riverdale
and all our camps abro how about makeup
and jewelry yes they can how about
braiding of the hair yes they can do
that also let's pick this up at Exodus
the thir
chapter Exodus the 3 chapter read that
verse 14 and then we go skip down and
let's see who it is that we talking
about here and what it is that he said
and this is going to talk a little bit
about the the jewels and the gold and
the rment ETC verse 14 go
ahead and God said unto Moses I am that
I am and he said th shallal thou say
unto the children of Israel I am have
sent me unto you there's a conversation
with the Lord and Moses and Moses was
saying hey Lord these people go ask me
you know what's your name he say just
tell them I am been around forever skip
down to verse 21 and pick it up there go
ahead and I will give this people favor
in the sight of the Egyptians and it
shall come to pass that when ye go ye
shall not go empty but every woman shall
borrow of her neighbor and of her that
sourn in her house jewels of silver
jewels of gold and rment and you shall
put them upon your sons and upon your
daughters and ye shall spoil the
Egyptians so this is when Israel was
leaving Egypt and the Lord said hey
you're not going to leave empty I'm
gonna make sure that you have jewels of
silver and jewels of gold and rment and
you can even put these things upon your
sons and upon your daughters turn over
to Exodus 32 Exodus the 32nd
chapter and when you get there I want
you to pick it up at that verse one this
is when we got in trouble with some of
this Jewels but this is what was allow
go ahead and when the people saw them
most delayed to come down out of the
mouth the people gathered themselves
together unto Aaron and said unto him up
make us Gods which shall go before us
for as forth this Moses the man that
brought us up out of the land of Egypt
we what not what is become of him shame
on them go ahead and Aaron said unto
them break out the Golden Earrings which
are in the ear of your wives of your
sons and of your daughters and bring
them unto me and all that the people
break off the gold of earring which were
in their ears and brought them unto
Aaron so I just wanted to show that they
had jewelry and they had earrings in and
all this good stuff going on now let's
turn over quickly to First Peter 3 last
place first Peter
3 1 Peter 3 and pick it up at that verse
one when you get there
first
3 and
one likewise ye wives be in subjection
to your own husband that if any obey not
the word they also May without the word
be one by the conversation of the wives
so if you a wife you got a husband a the
word just keep letting your light shine
he might be one over go ahead while they
behold your Chase conversation coupled
with fear whose adorning let it not be
that outward the Dy of platting the hair
and a wearing of gold or a putting on of
apparel so we talking about plating of
the hair or tanzel said plating of the
hair and wearing of gold we read that it
was allow and plating is another way
also of braiding as a form of braiding
the hair also so yeah it's allow you can
braid your hair go ahead verse four and
that's it but let it be the hidden man
of the heart and that which is not
corruptible e even the ordinance of a
Meek and quiet Spirit which is in the
sight of God of great price yeah so Lord
was just saying hey you put on all that
pretty stuff but you make sure that you
got a beautiful spirit working on the
inside that please God because it's of
great price so yeah you can wear pants
outside you wear makeup and jewelry and
braiding of the hair and things of that
nature that's all I
get and we hope that ansed your question
as we move on to our next one moving on
Randy Sims asked for explanation on
Deuteronomy
26:5 all right so brother Jerome give my
explanation on the Deuteronomy 26 and
verse
5 let's go read
it Deuteronomy 26
verse5 and thou sh speak and say before
the Lord thy God ayrian ready to perish
was my father and he went down into
Egypt and soured there with the few it
became there a nation Great Mighty and
populous okay that's talking about
um Jacob when he had um left from
Canaan and he
dwelt in Syria PanAm
Syria and there that's where the um 12
tribes came you know when he met
you know what that
Leah yeah and he had some concubines too
uh but that's where he went he went to
Syria okay let's go to uh Hosea chapter
12 and read verse 12 and
Hosea chapter 12 pick it up at verse 13
yeah and by a prophet the Lord brought
Israel out of Egypt and by a prophet was
he preserved Ephraim provoked him to
anger most bitterly therefore shall he
leave his blood upon him and his
reproach shall his Lord return unto him
now read verse 12 too and Jacob fled
into the country of Syria and Israel
served for a wife and for a wife he kept
sheep yeah so so yeah he fled he was
fleeing from his brother Esau and dwelt
uh in Syria and they became a uh a
nation there yeah that's all I got yeah
became a great nation I think only what
was it 70 Souls went down there and they
came out a great
nation all right brother thank you for
that hope that answered their question
as we move on to our next next one
Jennifer Love asks are funerals or
Memorial Services necessary
or is it totally up to the
person is it necessary a funeral is it
totally up to the person brother Dre
what you say well many of the the people
in the Bible have memorials and and
funerals for their loved
ones uh you could read about Abraham
dealing with Sarah and you could read
about Joseph and the children of Israel
dealing with their father
Jacob whose name is changed to Israel
and they saying that it was a great
morning for the Egyptians because they
look like the Egyptians however funerals
is a grievous thing to Bear you know for
a lot of people and it's a evil among
many things that came with sin but let's
go to ecclesiastics 9 and we going to
look at one verse there and then I got
one other place I want to go
Ecclesiastes 9 and I want you to read
verse three tanel Ecclesiastes 9 and
3 go ahead this is a evil among all
things that are done under the son that
there is one even unto all yeah also the
heart of the sons of men is full of evil
Madness is in their heart while they
live and after that they go to the dead
so this event happens to all nobody is
escapes this event and just like
life and living is a part of life so is
death you know but here's the the thing
about a funeral let's go to Ecclesiastes
7 Ecclesiastes 7 and I want you to read
uh verse two brother when you get there
verse
two it is better to go to the house of
mourning than to go to the house of
feasting
for that is the end of all men in the
living will I lay it to his heart so in
most cases while you memorializing your
family members a friend a loved one at a
funeral and talking about your memories
of them uh funerals are for the most
part for the living for us to lay it to
our hearts because that is something
that we all going to come to at some
point in life right and it says it's
better to go into the house of mourning
than the house of feasting but that is
the end of all men and those that are
living will lay it to his heart that
this is to come and if we lay it to our
heart maybe we'll see the urgency to do
what is right while we're living so that
we can live again verse four brother and
that is
it the heart of the wise is in the house
of mourning but the heart of fools is in
the House of M yeah the heart of the
wise is in the house of mourning because
they sit they can they considering how
fragile Life Is Right of foolish people
are in the House of
Mirth because they think life is just a
big old party and it ain't no
end but it is and then there's another
beginning that is eternal right when you
are in this life you have a chance to
lay it to
heart and I mean I could go on but I'll
pass with that other than read
ecclesiastics
12 it it it lets you know all
ecclesiastics nine it'll let you
know it's a living dog is better than a
dead lion because the living can lay it
to their heart so funerals are good in
the sense for us that are living to lay
it to our heart and consider our ways
and count our days so I I hope that
helps the the
question I like the question to be
answered again what did the question
say the question uh as are funerals or
Memorial Services necessary or is it
totally up to the
person if it was necessary to Bible was
said Thou shalt have a funeral and a
memorial but the Bible don't say that
all the brother said is good all of it
is good but the answer to the question
is it's
personal that's all I have to
say all right hope that answers your
question as we move on to our next
question next question Malik Shakur says
I had a friend that died 28 years ago
and never learned the trth truth will
God have mercy on people that have never
learned the
truth what you say brother Julius let's
see what the book say brother Cornel
let's go to Psalm let's go to Psalm
103 lord said he have mercy on whom he
will yeah but he is a merciful god tell
you that in the Commandments showing
mercies the thousands of those that keep
his commandment but you have to know
something Psalm 103 and verse 8 and then
I'm G move
on when you get it tenzel Psalm
1038 the Lord is merciful and gracious
slow to anger and plent is and mercy
let's go to
Romans Romans
10 maybe she you said she never learned
the truth maybe she heard the name maybe
she never understood
it Romans 10 read versus uh read verses
uh
13 for whosoever shall call upon the
name of the Lord shall be saved at the
appointed time go ahead for how then
shall they call on him in whom they have
not believed and how should they believe
in him of whom they have not heard right
you never heard truth how can she
believe but the Lord know go ahead and
how should they hear without a
preacher and how should they hear
without a preacher my last place
Jeremiah
17 Jeremiah 17 yes sir
Jeremiah chapter 17 my brother and pick
it up at verse 9 and 10 Jeremiah 17 n
and
10 the
heart the heart is deceitful above all
things and desperately wicked who can
know
it but I the Lord search the heart and
try the Reigns even to give every man
according to his ways and according to
the fruit of his doing so the Lord know
that's the answer the Lord know will the
Lord have mercy the Lord
know that's all I
got that's it all right hope that
answered your question as we move on to
our next question next question me too
for you Jones asked
in Ezekiel
16:
2-4 who are the people being mentioned
is it all the
Israelites so that Ezekiel 16 verses
2-4 who are the people being mentioned
here or is it all the Israelites let's
go there brother tanzel read that and
the guess caller would take it from
there the son of man caused Jerusalem to
know her abomination
and say thus say the Lord God to
Jerusalem thy birth and thy Nativity of
the land of Canaan thy father was an
Amorite and thy mother a hittite and as
for thy
negativity in the day that thou was born
thy neighor was not cut neither was thou
wash in water to Supple thee that was
not saled at all nor swat at
all that's St this strictly about Israel
nobody
else the answer is
yes okay so all Israel there all right
let's move on to our next question
sister next question melan uh natural
Journey says I know God want us to
forgive others how do we know we have
truly forgiven someone if we
did will we still think about what we
are supposed to forgive the person
for brother Julius forgiveness what you
say true forgiveness is when you no
longer hold a grudge have any resentment
or animosity toward whoever offended you
don't mean that you forget about it you
but you got to let go let's look at what
Matthew the 6th chapter say
tzel concerning FR
forgiveness Matthew chapter 6 I want you
to read my brother verse 12 and then we
G to skip to
14 Matthew 6 pay attention let's pay
attention to what we reading go ahead
and read and forgive us of our debts as
we forgive our debors forgive us of our
debt as we forgive our debt to us 14 for
if ye forgive men their trust passes
your heavenly father will also forgive
you because I have to forgive because I
don't want my I want the father to
forgive my sins so I have to forgive
somebody else 15 but if ye forgive not
men their trespasses neither will your
father forgive your trespasses if you
gonna hold on to those grudges and you
won't forgive think about what the book
just said that's all I
got all right hope that answered their
question as we move on to our next
question next question most love says
some people been in church all their
life like my Mom and Grandma it's hard
for them to accept the truth because
they never heard this before will God
understand and have
mercy all right been in church their
whole life which is a lot of cases with
a lot of people what you say Dre let's
go to Jeremiah 17 and we going to read
verse S and Skip and read nine and 10 go
ahead
brother Jeremiah
17 yep read verse
seven then skip nine and
10 blessed is the man that trusted in
the Lord and whose hope the Lord
is the heart is deceitful above all
things and desperately wicked who can
know it who can know the
heart go ahead
how the Lord search the high and I try
the Rings even to give every man
according to his ways and according to
the fruit of his doing it's the Lord
that knows the heart and he gonna search
it and he will try the Reigns and give
every man woman according to their ways
and their doings let's go to Revelation
20 and read verses 12 and
13 Revelation
20 vers 12 and 13
sir and I saw the dead small and great
stand before God and the books were open
and another book was open which is The
Book of Life and the dead were judge out
of those things which were written in
the books according to their
works and the Sea gave of the Dead which
were in it and death and Hell delivered
up the dead which were in them and they
were judged every man according to their
works
and we just read that it is the Lord
that searching the heart and he will
judge them
according and the Lord will have mercy
on whom he have will have mercy and who
he don't they will have none but it is
the Lord that is search that out so the
answer is that is between them and
God that's all I
got right brother Dre we just hope that
you know Harden not their heart like the
Lord say everybody got to harden out
your heart when you want to receive this
truth all right thank you for that
brother our next question sister next
question Jennifer Love asks can you guys
provide the chronological order of the
end times example what comes first the
first resurrection the Wilderness Etc
and is the Book of Revelation the best
place to find this
all right guest caller can you share
some
light sure want to know the chronical
then you should pay attention to to
what's being
taught but we will show you but we will
show you a quick
synopsis of The Chronicles of things go
to Matthew's 24th
chapter and we going to read first 3
through five and we're going to skip
Matthew
24 24
325 and as he said upon the out of ol
the disciples came unto him privately
saying tell us when shall these things
be and what shall be the sign of thy
coming and of the end of the world and
Jesus answered and said unto them take
heed that no man deceive you for many
shall come in my name saying I am Christ
and shall deceive many
so the first thing he did is warn you
about lying preachers but here are the
signs skip down to verse 15 and read
it and when ye therefore shall see the
abomination of desolation spoken of by
Daniel the Prophet stand in the Holy
Place whoo readeth let him
understand okay so the holy place that's
in the temple that's the temple that
these people that call themselves Jews
are going to be built
and the Abomination that's going to
stand in it is the pope of Rome because
once they build that Temple some kind of
way the European Union is going to
install that Pope into that Temple then
you will see the
abomination of De desolation standing in
the Holy place and short you see Pope uh
uh setting up house in the temple that
is the first order of things now what's
going to happen when you get that skip
down to verse 21 and go ahead
for then shall be Great Tribulation such
as was not since the beginning of the
world to this time no nor ever shall
be and except those days should be
shortened there shall be no flesh be
saved but for the elect sake those days
shall be
shortened so now when the pop moving
there he they going call these people
that call themselves Jews going to start
down a sacrifice he moving that the
temple they going to stop the animal
sacrifice and he is going
to start what's called a Great
Tribulation that's going to last for
three and a half
years and what's going to put the end of
this three and a half of Great
Tribulation coming of Jesus skip down to
verse
29 and read
29 29 and
30 immediately after the tribul of those
days shall the sun be darkened and the
moon shall not give her light and the
Stars shall fall from Heaven and the
powers of Heaven shall be
shaken and then shall appear the sign of
the son of man in heaven and then shall
all the tribes of the earth mourn and
they shall see the son of man coming in
the Clouds Of Heaven with power and
great
Glory so now that's going to end the
three and A2 years of Great Tribulation
when Jesus show up going to roll back
like a scroll Sun's going to turn black
and the moon going to turn red and here
come Jesus and during that time you have
also your first resurrection go to first
Thessalonians the 4th chapter read
verses 16 and
17 for the Lord himself shall descend
from heaven with the Shout with the
voice of the Archangel and with the
Trump of God and the dead in Christ
shall rise first
then we which are alive and remain shall
be caught up together with them in the
clouds to meet the Lord in the air and
so shall we ever ever be with the
Lord now that's going to be the first
resurrection you're going to build a
temple in Jerusalem Pope going to move
into it he going to bring three and a
half years of Destruction on this Earth
the Lord's going to come and take him
down and when the Lord's coming that's
when you going had a first
resurrection let going to end the Great
Tribulation that's calleda by the Beast
and the false prophet now let's go
quickly to uh back to Matthew the 24th
chapter and read verse
31 he shall send his angels with the
great sound of a trumpet and they shall
gather together his elect from the Four
Winds from one end of Heaven to the
other now once he get back on this Earth
that's what he going to start recovering
is Israel and let's see where it's going
to take them the last place of Ezekiel
the 20th
chapter and we're going to read verse 33
to
36 Ezekiel 20th
chapter 33
36 as I live say the Lord God surely
with a mighty hand and with a stretched
out arm and with Fury poured out will I
rule over you and I will bring you out
from the people and will gather you out
of the country wherein you are scattered
with the mighty hand and with the
stretched out arm and with Fury poured
out I will bring you into the Wilderness
of the people and there would I plead
with you face to face like as I pleaded
with your fathers in the wilderness of
the land of Egypt so would I plead with
you sayeth the Lord
God so now that's the order of things
you going to build a temple in Jerusalem
hope going to move into it then he going
to bring three and a half years of Great
Tribulation on this Earth the Lord's
going to come and take him out in the
Lord and in the meantime when the Lord
coming you going to have the first
resurrection because the living going to
be Chang and the dead going to be raised
to meet the Lord in a so once the Lord
come and he is on this Earth then he set
going to set us and the second time to
recover Israel and he going to take them
into the wilderness
before they go into the land that's the
chronological order of
things that's all I have to say all
right thank you for that light I'm sure
that answered that question as we move
on to our next question yes next
question Valencia asks when I am talking
about the Lord's word with someone and
they don't want to hear what you have to
say do I leave them alone or keep trying
to talk to them and second
Timothy 23 verse 24 is
given what verse is
given second Timothy
23 verse
24 we don't have no second Timothy
23 verse 24 but what we will do is still
give some scriptures that will answer
the question so can you read the
question again Deborah yes when I am
talking about the Lord's word with
someone and they don't want to hear what
you have to say do I have do I leave
them alone or keep trying to talk to
them all right well somebody tell you if
they don't want to hear the word then
you should respect that and just leave
them alone maybe they come back to you
later and maybe um then they have an ear
to hear but you can't force it on them
and and make them hear you out but let's
go to Titus Titus the third
chapter because you saying when you
talking the Lord's word with someone
they don't want to hear it you know
should you leave them alone Titus 3 and
read verse 10 and 11 because right now
they can be a heretic they can be
contrary against the word word of God we
don't know what might happen down the
road but read verse 10 and 11 for me go
ahead and a man that is inherited after
the first and second admonition reject
uhuh he that is such is subverted and
sinth being condemned to of himself so
are they contrary against so they don't
want to hear and after you go to them
the first time and maybe the second and
they don't want to hear hey leave him
alone let's turn over to Romans 14
Romans the 14th
chapter Romans sometimes people don't
want to hear what you have to say and
you have to respect that right Romans 14
and let's pick it up at that verse seven
and let's see who it is that they belong
to whether they want to hear it don't
want to hear it whether they live
whether they
die read verse um seven for me go ahead
for none of us liveth to himself and no
man dieth to himself uhhuh but whether
we live we live unto the Lord and
whether we die we die unto the Lord but
whether we live therefore or die we are
the Lords one more verse for to the end
Christ both died and Rose and reviv that
he might be Lord both of the dead and
living so if somebody you know don't
want to hear it hey whether they live or
die they belong unto the Lord and like
the brothers been saying since the show
been on hey maybe the mercy of the Lord
will shine through on them but if they
don't want to hear it leave them be and
hey hopefully they'll come back to you
at a later time but now is not the time
for them that's all I
got could somebody go and read what
Jesus said don't cast your Pearls Before
Swine all right yeah that
that's definitely need to be r
we're in search mode for that be coming
up with that shortly seven and Matthew 7
and6 yeah Matthew 7 and
six Matthew 7 verse six give not that
which is holy unto the dogs either cast
you your Pearls Before Swine th they
trample them under their feet and turn
again and ren
you see so if you keep trying to push
something on somebody and they don't
want it they might be a swine
in other words they going to get you
don't leave them alone then they going
they going to trample the word talk
about it then they going to turn around
and attack you yeah if not physically
Spirit mentally so if they don't want to
hear it you're cashing your prayer
before
swin yeah take that sweet holy word just
hold on to it and hey if they come back
you'll be ready for them and that's the
word of Jesus yes right yes sir all
right thank you for that add on hope
that answered their question as we move
on to our next one moving on Mrs K Kathy
ask in Isaiah 41 verse one the location
o island is this any land away from
Jerusalem o Island brother Julius what
you got
you on mute
brother let's go to Isaiah 41 and read
our scripture Isaiah 41 Isaiah 41 and
then uh we gonna go to uh Esther
10 when you get it 10 Isaiah 41
And1 keep silence before me oh Island
and let the people renew their strength
let them come near let them speak let us
come near together to
judgment so now a island is a piece of
land surrounded by water let me show you
what I'm talking about Jerusalem is on
the main land is on the land of uh is in
the land of Israel and it's called the
land of Canaan that's the the name of we
call it Israel today let's go to Esther
10 And1
let's see where the Islands are located
Esther 10 and wi when you get it go
ahead and the king of bazus laid a
tribute upon the land and upon the a of
the sea a is abbreviation for Islands so
you got an example of island is Jamaica
on the Caribbean Sea in the
Mediterranean Sea you have cre and
Cyprus under the Mediterranean Sea uh
you got uh Japan which is separated from
the mainland of Europe but a part of
Europe but in it's it's on the sea so
that's what it is so it is uh separated
from Israel Israel is on the main land
and an island is something a land
surrounded by water I hope that
helped all right hope that answer that
question sister Deborah our next
question with the time check yes the
next question a 12 is the time Jennifer
Love says since I am a newbie to the
truth and excited about learning more I
have lost contact with my family and
socalled friends I feel alone and find
myself so isolated and sad any
suggestions well welcome newbie don't
give up on the truth brother Jerome what
you got definitely let's let's go to um
Matthew's the 12th chapter read verse
48- 50 and then we going to do the 10th
chapter after
that Serv of the Lord had to make this
Choice it's called bearing your cross
you know and standing for your God you
know when everything seemed to be
against you you know Matthew 12:48
through
50 but he answered and said to him that
told him who is my mother and who are my
brethren and he stretched forth his hand
towards his disciples and said behold my
mother and my
brethren whosoever shall do the will of
My Father which is in heaven the same as
my brother and sister and
mother yeah through the will of through
the will of the father and you going to
suffer some persecution when you do that
even with your family with your friends
okay so now let's tie that with the 10th
chapter and read verse
33-39 whoever shall deny me before men
him would I also deny before my Father
which is in heaven but think not that I
am come to send peace on Earth I came
not to send peace but a
sword for I am come to set a man at
variance against his father and the
daughter against her mother and the
daughter-in-law against her
mother-in-law
go that's going to do the separating
that's what that's what's going to
happen go
ahead and a man F shall shall be they of
his own
household but he that loveth father or
Mo mother more than me is not worthy of
me and he that love a son or a daughter
more than me is not worthy of
me and he that taketh not his cross and
follow after me is not worthy of me and
he that find of his life shall lose it
and he that loseth his life for my sake
shall find
it forsake he say Lord we have forsaken
us with the uh Apostles Lord we have
forsaken all and follow thee so we had
to do the same thing that's right that's
that's all I
got can we read one verse in that uh
first Peter
4 and verse 14 first 1 Peter 4 and4 One
verse
and if you be reproached for the name of
Christ happy are ye for the spirit of
glory and of God rested upon you for
their part he is evil spoken of but on
your part he is
glorified so you just hang on all that
excitement you say about finding this
truth and like brother Jerome say expect
some of this little separation and
persecution but you stay happy because
hey God is with you that's right all
right hope that answered your question
as we move on to our next one next one
Barbara steel says why do we dispute
what the Bible says when it says the
Angels defiled themselves and took
themselves dot dot dot why would it say
it if it's not true all right why do
people dispute what the Bible say not us
but people brother Dre what you say
well I can't answer for what people do
but what what I'd like for you to do is
give us chapter and verse for what
you're saying that the Bible that we're
disputing about angels defiling
themselves so when you give us chapter
and verse we will address the question
it's kind of vague what you asking dot
dot dot I can't decipher it and I don't
want to assume what you're saying so
please
resubmit right all right hope that that
um will have you to resubmit and brother
Dre will address it then moving on to
our next question next question philis
Campbell asks according to 2 Corinthians
10: 4 and five how do you pull down
strongholds and cast down every
imagination that exalts itself against
the knowledge of God to bring into
captivity all right good question there
2 Corinthians 10 let's go there brother
tanzel read that verse 4 and five and
the guest caller go share some light on
how is it that you cast down every evil
imagination that
exist for the weapons of our Warfare are
not carnal But Mighty through God
through the pce down a
stronghold casting down imagination and
every High thing that exalt itself
against the knowledge of God and
bringing into captivity every thought to
The Obedience of
Christ let's show you how to do that
first let go into Ephesians the 6th
chapter read verses 13- 17
Ephesians 6 ver 13-1
17 wherefore take unto you the whole
armor of God that he may be able to
withstand in the evil day and having
done all to stand so stand therefore
having your loins G about with truth and
having on the
bre first thing is you have to know what
the truth is if you according to the
Bible if you learn G with truth you have
to
know what is true right in the word of
God go ahead and having on the
breastplate of
righteousness and you got to live it
just can't know what truth is and don't
do it then you got to walk in it go
ahead and your feet shy with the
preparation of the gospel of
peace and you always want preach the
gospel of God and make peace go ahead
above all taking the shield of faith
where if ye shall be able to quench all
the fiery dos of the wicked and you got
to believe everything that you read that
God showed you that's the shield of
Faith because if you don't have no faith
somebody will knock you off the dime but
the big thing is coming up now go ahead
and read and take the helmet of
salvation and the sword of the spirit
which is the word of
God but take the heaven of Salvation And
what the sword of the spirit the sword
of the spirit and that is the word of
God that's right you have
to now let's go one last place let's go
into Hebrews the 4th chapter and read
verse
12 Hebrew fourth chapter and pick it up
at verse
12 but the word of God is quick and
Powerful and charar than any twoed
sword piercing even to the dividing the
sun of Souls and spirit and of the
joints and Marrow and is a discernment
of the thoughts and intent of the
heart so that's the word of God it will
bring down every
lie it will change every
falsehood it will cut it down just like
cutting your arm off okay
every thought into captivity of the word
of God by knowing the word of God and
crushing Every Lie that's been told
that's all I have to say with the word
of
God all right if that answers your
question as we move on to our
next next one Mark Ash says how many
times did Jesus appear on Earth as a man
in the Old Testament did he appear to
Abraham in Genesis 18 verse2 with the
two angels and as mesed or anywhere
else all right I know they ask about
Genesis 18 and2 let's go there read that
and the guest caller would take it from
there Genesis 18 and2
and he lifted up his eyes and look and
lo three men stood by him and when he
saw them he ran to meet
them from the tent door and bowed
himself towards the
ground so now the B the Bible said three
men two of them was Angels if you keep
reading and one was the Lord because
Abraham bargained with him trying to
save Sodom and
G sure one time the Lord showed up as a
man but he was not a man and the other
time as MC when he made Abraham from the
slaughter of the kings that knocked off
Sodom and
S so that
also was the Lord go to Hebrews the 7th
chapter and start reading at verse
one Hebrews 7th
chapter for this m ke a day king of
Salem preach of the most high God who
met Abraham returning from the slaughter
of the Kings and blessed
them to whom also Abraham gave a t part
of all first being by interpretation
king of righteousness and after that
also king of Salem which is king of
peace without father without mother
without descent having neither beginning
of days nor end of life but made like
unto the son of God a body for priest
continually now so ELC also showed up
and uh uh in the form of a man but we
know that he was not because he had no
beginning of days or the end of life and
so when so I know those two times if
it's
anymore then I tell the the the person
that asked the question find them and
show and and go you can read the Bible
just like I can
that's all I have to say all right hope
that aners your question sister Deborah
we're going into new
territory yes we are we are now into
tonight's Q&A for Wednesday January the
22nd
2025 ran
64s in Colossians 1 vers
15-8 is it only talking about Christ
who created everything or this also
talking about God also who created
everything brother Jerome share some
light let's go read that Colossians 115
through
[Music]
18 who is the image of the invisible God
the first born of every
creature right there that's letting you
know that's the Lord he say the
firstborn of every Every Creature he was
the first one to be a flesh and blood
man and become God go ahead but by him
were all things created and are in
heaven and that are in Earth visible and
invisible whether they be Thrones or
Dominion or principalities or Powers all
things were created by Him and for him
and he is before all things and by him
all things
consist and he is the head of the body
the church who is the beginning the
firstborn from the dead that in all
things he might have the preeminence and
again right there that verse let you
know that's talking about the one that
became the son Jesus Christ because the
father never died the son came and died
for us and then rose on the third day
okay uh so let's let's go to uh
Ephesians 3:9 so we can kind of
understand about the creation because
there there be confusion about what did
the father do the creation or did the
son do the creating let's go to
Ephesians the 3 chapter verse 9 it'll
clear it
up get it go ahead and
read what was that again Ephesians 3
yeah verse
9 and to make all men see what is the
Fellowship of the the mystery which from
the beginning of the world have been hid
in God who created All Things by Jesus
Christ so
it's Jesus Christ is the hand of the
father that created everything that was
created and let's tie that with that uh
St John 1 verse one and two and that'll
be
it than John
one the beginning was the word and the
Word was God
and the Word was God the same was in the
beginning with
God go ahead keep reading verse three
all things were made by him and without
him was not anything made that was
made and Skip down to verse
14 and the Word was made flesh and dwelt
among us and we beheld his glory the
glory as of the only begotten of the
father full of grace and truth yeah so
the father created All Things by the
hand of Jesus
Christ that's all I
got all right thank you for that
Brothers we move on to our next question
next question natley Charles asks do
angels eat will we once again eat Angels
food in the
wilderness and psalm 78:2
is
given yeah we know that Angels eat and
whether or not we go eat Angels food in
the
wilderness I don't know but let's go and
see do angel e first that's the first
part of the question let's go into that
uh Genesis
19 because this again is when uh the
Angels were dealing with lot here for
the destruction of Sodom and gamorra so
let's go in that Genesis
19 and let's see who was there with lot
and what it was that lot said he wanted
to do for them go ahead brother Genesis
19 and verse
one and there came two angels to Sodom
at Ed and lot sat in the gate of Sodom
and lot seeing them rose up to meet them
and he bowed himself with his face
towards the ground so two angels came at
lot and he um bowed himself to them and
then what did he say in verse two
and he said behold now my Lord turn in I
pray you into your Servants house and T
all night and wash your feet and you
shall rise up early and go on your ways
and they said nay but we will abide in
the streets all night uhhuh and he
pressed upon them greatly and they
turned in unto him and entered into his
house and he made them a feast and did
bake unleavened bread and they did eat
so yeah the Angels did when lot made
them a feast he say and he made them a
feast and he did break un B unle bread
and they did eat so yeah the Angels did
eat there with lot so we know that the
Angels do eat it's their choice now
let's turn over to Psalm 78 that they
put in here Psalm 78 Psalm
78 when you get there brother read that
one verse 25 Psalm 78 and 2
go
ahead man did eat Angels food and he
sent them meat to the
full okay man did eat Angels food and he
sent them meat to the fool and you
asking whether or not that will happen
again in the wilderness I don't know and
that's all I got anybody else like to
add okay so we're going to leave it
right there and we're going to move on
to our next question next question
Barbara steel
says where did you see that God was
going to assist us in getting to the
Wilderness Julius where did you see that
God was going to assist us in getting to
the Wilderness the book say Jesus Christ
the same yesterday today and forever and
he changes not let's look let's look at
how he did it in the old in the old days
let's go to Exodus the 13th chapter
kzel when we get there let's let's pick
it up at Verse
18 when you get it my brother go ahead
Exodus 13 and 18 go ahead and read for
God let the people about through the way
of the Wilderness of the Red Sea and the
children of Israel went up harness out
of the land of Egypt skip down to verse
20 and go ahead and they took their
Journey from sukov and encamp in Eden
and the edge of the
Wilderness and the Lord went before them
by day in a pillar of cloud to lead them
to lead them the way and by night in a
pillar of fire to give them light to go
by day and
night and he took not away the pillar of
cloud by day nor the pillar of Fire by
night from before so the Lord had his
angels working in there you know that
was the Lord working through his angels
cuz he always have his angels of
protection let's go to Exodus the night
chapter pardon me Exodus the 19th
Chapter read verse one and then we going
skip to verse three go
ahead and the third morning when the
children of Israel were gone forth out
of the land of Egypt the same day came
they into Wilderness of Si to the
Wilderness right skip down to verse
three go ahead and Moses went up unto
God and the Lord called unto him out of
the mountain saying thus shall thou say
to the house of Jacob and tell the
children of Israel you have seen what I
did unto the Egyptian and how I bear you
on Eagle wings and brought you into up
to myself so now he said I bear your
Eagles Wing meaning I had my angels
working on your behalf I bought you all
by great power that's what the Eagles
Wing represent so how the Lord going to
do it in these days Matthew the 24th
chapter he don't change Matthew 24 and
pick it up at verse 30 my
brother when the Lord return what he say
he GNA
do and then shall appear the sign of the
son of man in heaven and then shall all
the tribes of the earth mourn and they
shall see the son of man coming in the
Clouds Of Heaven with power and great
glory and he shall s and he shall sent
his angels with a great Trump a great
sound of a trumpet and they shall gather
together is elect from the Four Winds
from one end of Heaven to the other but
before we go before that happen we going
back to the Wilderness the Lord going to
fix it so we going to by we going to go
back to the Wilderness by ships and by
boat by ships and by boats list them
brothers so therefore he going to do the
same thing he going to do the same thing
and when you get there he going to have
his angels protecting you there that's
all I got for right now
let me all right brother
Julius caller go right
ahead one other thing let's go the 11th
chapter yes
sir and
uh start at verse
uh
11 it's talking about Jesus here
shall come to pass in that day that the
Lord shall set his hand against the
second time to recover the remnant of
his people which shall be left from
Assyria and from Egypt and from Pathos
and from Kush and from El and from
shanar and from HTH and from the islands
of the
sea now who whose hand the Lord whose
hand going to do this the
Lord he said yeah is going to and he
named all of these
countries that mean just like he brought
us out of Egypt he is going to set his
hand a second
time to bring us from all over the world
yes sir that's all I have to say you
that's call because we know his power is
unlimited all right hope that ansed your
question as we move on to our next one
next one little mama Hayes ass mess up
potamia is the region of the tiger River
in the area of the garden of eeden were
they
Gentiles
Julius that Mesopotamia is also
surrounded by the Euphrates river and
all that region was called ancient
Babylon at that time look like the
hammock occupied that
land I don't know who was in there other
day probably a bunch of people but
that's all I got on that read in Genesis
the 10th chapter where Ham's children
had had had that
area Gentiles are the children of
japat okay we'll leave it right there as
we move on to our next next one natley
Charles asks can you explain the essence
of a comforter or Holy Spirit ghost I
heard people refer to the spirit as a
Revelation from God others refer to the
spirit as Angels specifically
Gabriel yes
Cara well the spirit of God comes in in
a lot of form the breath that you
breathe is called Spirit the thoughts of
the mind is Spirit but since you use the
word comforter then we going to the
angel but even the Bible said God is a
spirit Jesus to you the words that I
speak they are spirit and they are life
but when but because the confidence is
thrown in here then that puts it well in
the hand of the
Angel let's first go to St John the 16th
chapter read verse 7 and then we're
going to skip down and read verse 12-
15 nevertheless I tell you the truth is
expedient for you that I go away but if
I go not away the comforter will not
come unto you but if I depart I will
send him unto you do that mean his
comforter is sent by
Jesus he don't come on his own he is
sent he I go it's a speeding I go
nevertheless you know there a speeding
because I got to go when I go if I don't
go the comforter won't come to you but
I'm gonna send him to you what verse was
that that was end
s get down to verse 12 that's uh yeah 12
go ahead I have yet many things to say
unto you but ye cannot bear them now how
be it when he the spirit of Truth is
come and he will guide you into all
Truth for he shall not speak of himself
but whatsoever he shall hear that shall
he speak and he sh he will show you
things to come
he should glorify me for he shall
receive of mine and shall show it unto
you all things that the father have are
are mine therefore said I that he shall
take of mine and shall show it unto
you so now when he send his comforter he
is not going to speak his own words he
going to speak only the word which Jesus
given but then Jesus the word that Jesus
speak is the Father's that's why he said
when he come he going to show you mine
they said all the fathers have is mine
so let's go and look at this the way
this really P out go into
Revelations first
chapter read verses 1 two and we're
going to skip down to verse 10 and
11 verse one and two first
the revelation of Jesus Christ which God
gave unto him now now revelation of
Jesus Christ with what who gave it to
him
God God gave it to him go ahead and read
to show unto his servant things which
must shortly come to pass uh and he sent
and signified it by his
Angel unto his servant
John who bear record of the word of God
and of the testimony of Jesus Christ and
of all things that he
saw so now we have a protocol right
there father gave it to Jesus Jesus gave
gave it to the Angel and the angel
brought it to man just like we just read
in St John 16 they said it confident you
have many things to give
you and uh you know when he come he
going to take a mind and he going to
give it to you all that the father have
is
mine father gave to Jesus Jesus gave to
him Ang and Angels brought it to man now
skip down to verse 10 and read it
101 I was in the spirit on the Lord's
day and heard behind me a great voice of
a
trumpet saying I am Alpha and Omega the
first and the last and what thou seest
write in the book and send it unto the
seven churches which are in Asia unto
Ephesus and unto smyna
and unto pergamos and unto Thia and unto
Sardis and unto Philadelphia and unto
leosia he said I want you to send it to
all seven of these
churches now let's see what method that
he use to send to these
churches let's go into Revelation the 2
chapter read
one then skip down and read seven
and8 verse verse one
unto the angel of the Church of Ephesus
write these things say he that holdeth
the Seven Stars in his right hand who
walketh in the midst of the seven golden
candlesticks so we know that's Jesus
let's see what he said now he sent him a
message now once he got through the me
with with the message let's see how it
ended skip down to verse
S read it he that have an ear let him
hear what the spirit saith unto the
churches
to him that
overcome finish it to him that
overcometh will I give to eat of the
tree of life which is in the midst of
the paradise of
God now that's one church I ain't going
to send him to another church read uh uh
verse
eight and unto the angel of the church
in Smyrna right these things said the
first and the last which was dead and is
alive
now he gave a message let's see how he
ended the
message skip down to verse 11 and read
he that have an ear let him hear what
the spirit say unto the churches he that
overcome go
ahead he that overcometh shall not be
hurt of the second
death
okay he ended the same way now let's go
into re Revelations 3r chapter read
verse
one and until the angel of the church
and S is right these things said these
things said he that have the seven
spirit of God and the Seven Stars I Know
Thy works that thou has a name that thou
livest and are
dead but now let see how that message
when he got through with that message
what did it say skip down and read verse
six
he that have an ear let him hear what
the spirit sath unto the
churches okay so now he gave a message
to the last
church and let's see what that says skip
down to verse 22 he sent a message to
the last Church what does it say he that
have an ear let him hear what the spirit
sayth unto the
churches through all these messages is
sent to the church was B to them by the
spirit
now let's see what this spirit is called
go to Revelation chap 22 and read verse
16 I Jesus have sent my angel to testify
unto you these things in the churches I
am the root and The Offspring of David
and the bright and Morning
Star okay so the confidence the spirit
of Truth
and the angel is one and the same that's
why the Lord worked through him he get
the message from the father then he
grabbed the angel and sent him to
man just like he did all of these
churches every one of and every message
he sent was sent by an Angel and an
angel is a spirit because the Lord say
he maketh his Angel Spirit that's why he
kept saying he that have an ear let him
hear what the spirit said to the
churches and we read revelation 22 and6
we find out that spirit that was talking
to the churches is the Angel of the Lord
that he sent which is also called the
comforter that's so I have to
say
man we lost
corneel all right then we will go to the
next question which is from tomor
Williams tomarrow Williams asks
according to the Bible
did it take God 6,000 years to create
the world and Mankind or was it six days
I believe Jerome has that
one yeah um before he
created uh
light you know the Lord had created the
heavens and the Earth
already okay before he created light all
right so let's go read that let's go to
Genesis the first
chapter pick it up at verse one read it
to the
three in the beginning God created the
Heaven and the Earth and the Earth was
without form and void and darkness was
upon the face of the deep and the spirit
of God moved upon the face of the
waters and God said let there be light
and there was light see the heaven in
the Earth the Heaven and the Earth was
already in existence before he even
created light okay go ahead and God saw
the light that it was good and God
divided the light from the darkness uhuh
and God called the light day and the
Darkness he called night and the evening
and the morning were the first day so
that's when he created light then he
started dealing with uh the days like
when you was mentioning in your question
about the
uh the six days and the day of the Lord
is a thousand years so let's go read
that hold your place in this Genesis
we'll come back uh go to that second
Peter verse
three uh chapter 3 and read verse 8
second Peter chapter 3
ver8 but beloved be not ignorant of this
one thing that one day is with the Lord
as a thousand years and a thousand years
as one day yeah now back to that Genesis
and pick it up at the verse four and
read it to the
five and God saw the light that it was
good and God divided the light from the
darkness and God called the light day in
the darkness he called night and the
evening and the morning were the first
day yeah and each day it was a thousand
years to the Lord so then when you read
it all the way through to the sixth day
he tell you all the things that he had
done all the things he had created and
made within those days and then he
rested on the seven you know we know he
created man on on the uh fourth
day that's all I got
on all right thank brother answer that
question as we move on moving on me to
you
me too for you Janes says I noticed that
the Hebrew calendar has a month called
tamuz in my Bible dictionary it says
Samaran Pagan God is the calendar being
used a Samarian
calendar all right guess
calling Cal we make is not the Samaran
Cal I know know that tamas is the name
of of of the child supposed to be by
Simas and N Nimrod supposed to be the
greatest child ever been born even in
Ezekiel is talking about saw some women
weeping for
Tamar
however we don't you we make our own
calendar at the Israel of God and we
don't even use the name toas we when we
get to that month we call call it the
fourth
M so whatever the other Hebrews or
whatever call them is doing
with they coun that's up to them but we
don't use the name toas the name that
they call Tomas is the fourth month so
we use that's the only month that we
don't use a name we said it's the fourth
month I can't speak for any other
anybody else but I can speak for the
Israeli God that's all I have to say
all right as we move on to our next
question yes uh Zion question was
answered uh
earlier uh with the
timeline but he says the question he has
was while we are in the wilderness for
those three and a half years will that
be the time the pope is in the temple or
is that the time that Jesus will punish
the evildoers
yes
carer no the uh uh uh the F GNA be taken
out before the uh uh uh before the uh uh
the Lord come let's go to 2
Thessalonians the 2
chapter and we're going to start reading
at verse I mean the second chapter I'm
sorry second Thessalonians the second
chapter and we're going to start reading
at verse one
second Thessalonians the 2 chapter and
verse one so let you know that uh uh
these are two different times all
together when you get there read it
second Thessalonians the 2 chapter and
we're going to start reading at verse
one okay
go now we besee you Brethren by the
coming of our Lord Jesus Christ and by
Gathering Together unto him that you be
not that you be not soon shaken in mind
or be troubled neither by Spirit nor by
word nor by letter as from us as that
the day of Christ is at
hand telling you right now he's telling
you right now you know people talking
about Christ can come any day and Christ
can come at that time he said look we're
telling you don't believe it I don't
care if you get a word from us or by
Spirit or by letter or anything anything
else that Jesus that the coming of Jesus
at hand because these things have to be
done before Jesus come keep reading let
no man deceive you by any means for that
day shall not come except there come a
falling away first and that that man of
sin is revealed the son of
predition who oppose and exalt himself
above all that is called God all
that hello
that's why it said
look this against man of sin have to
come
first okay the son of Destruction that's
what the predition is okay now to start
back over uh uh verse four and go
ahead who oppose and exalt himself above
all that is called God or that is
worship so that he as God sth in the
temple of God showing himself that he is
God now that let you know that this guy
going to come now this is the this is
the pop he's in the temple of God and he
going to show himself to be God and he
is going to do it
for three and a half years keep keep
reading remember ye not that when I was
yet with you I told you these things and
now ye know what withholden that he
might be revealed in his
time for the mystery of iniquity do
already
work but only he who now leth will let
until he be taken out of the
way uhuh and then shall that Wicked be
reveal whom the Lord shall consume with
the spirit of his mouth shall destroy
with the brightness of his
coming so
now so now Jesus before his feet the
ground he is going to take this guy out
Revelation 19th Chapter tell you the
Beast and the false prophet he going to
cast him alive into the Lake of Fire so
this guy going to have his three and a
half years of Great Tribulation then
Jesus going to come and he is going to
take him out through him in the Lake of
Fire then Jesus will set his hand the
second time to recover his
people and he going to take him into the
Wilderness and plead with him face to
face till now in three and a half years
is before Jesus come in fact when Jesus
come we going to put an end to this
guy's three and a half years and then he
will start his three and A2 years
Ministry in the wilderness that is the
order that's all I gotta say all right
thank you for that hope that answered
that question next question next
question uh daughter of Judah says 10
years ago I came into the truth I sto
stop attending Sunday church so my
husband stopped going too he won't join
me in Sabbath online studies but would
go back to the church we were members
for the Sunday service we have no
spiritual Foundation as a married couple
and is taking a big toll on our marriage
would it be wrong to attend Sunday
service with him even though I will
still keep the Sabbath I feel like some
truth for him will be better than no
Truth at all they teach from the
KJV but don't deserve the Sabbath
brother Dre what you say question is
what are they teaching they going to
church on Sunday you've been 10 years
out of it and you have been
enduring and doing what is right and you
have been an example to what's right and
you got to endure sister you got to walk
in this word and be an example of one
that's walking in the
word why would you go to a place that
you know is teaching
wrong you know truth mixed with a lie is
still a
lie end of the day it's just mixed with
an untrue let's go to uh Matthew 10
Matthew
10 and pick it up at verse 34 Matthew 10
and
34 go ahead brother but think not that I
am come to send peace on Earth I came
not to send peace but a
sword but I am come to set a man ADV
Vance against his father and a
daughter-in-law against her mother and
the mother and the daughter-in-law
against her
mother-in-law and a man F shall be day
of his own
household but he that love a father or
mother more than me is not worthy of me
and he that love a son or a daughter
more than me is not worthy of
me and he that taketh not his cross and
follow after me is not worthy of me but
he that findeth his life shall lose it
and he that loseth his life for my sake
shall find it that's right so you got a
war and that war that sword of is the
sword of the spirit the word of God it
can divide or it can bring together and
what what you can do is continue to be
patient with your husband and be an
example of one following the word of God
let's go to uh Hebrews 10 Hebrews
10 and pick it up at verse 36 brother go
ahead when you get it but ye have need
of patience that after have done the
will of God ye might receive the promise
you might say well hey I've been patient
for 10
years hey just continue to be patient
and walk in that word go ahead for yet a
little while and he that shall come will
come and will not
t now the just shall live by faith but
if any man draw back my soul shall have
no pleasure in him why would you draw
back to a Sunday church that you know is
not teaching the
truth don't do that sister just be an
example love your
husband do what's right by your husband
and walk in this
word I hope that helps yeah brother
verse
39 go Ahad finish verse 39 go ahead
brother but we are not of them who draw
back un pred
but of them that believe to the saving
of the Soul Ure sister but guest caller
go
ahead yeah you know you have to find the
scripture where Paul is telling you that
about uh uh uh about pagan gods he says
pagan gods are nothing we know that but
he tell you in other words you have to
watch but uh what you do because other
people are watching
you it's uh the we I can't think of the
scripture right now maybe somebody can
pull it up if you can think well Paul
tell me if uh somebody put up in front
of you and then say that this is
whatever you put in front of you uh eat
uh uh without asking question but if
they say that this is dedicated to some
God don't
eat then he go you know somebody can
find that then he going tell you that
the uh uh that you have to be careful
you stumble your brother
I think it's First Corinthians
8 let's look at it and see First
Corinthians 8 and
uh four eight and
four
okay as concerning therefore the eating
of those things that are offered in
sacrifice under Idols we know that an
idol is nothing in the world and that
there is none other God but one but
though there be that are called Gods
whether in heaven or in earth as there
be Gods many and Lords many but to us
there is but one God the father of whom
are all things and we in him and one
Lord Jesus Christ by whom are all things
and we by
him how be it there is not in every man
the knowledge of some with conscience of
the idols unto this hour eating as a
thing offered unto an idol and their
conscience being weak is
defile but meat commendeth us not to God
for neither if we eat are we the better
neither if we eat not are we the
worst but take
he right here the seven verses is what
you got to pay attention to it how be it
there is not in every man that that
knowledge you know for some uh uh for
some with conscience of the idol let me
see for for for some with conscience of
the idol
unto his hour eat it as a thing of
offered unto an
idol their conscious being weak is
defile but is really saying is you know
that the that what they dealing with is
paganism you know they D is nothing
however somebody been watching you
walking in line and doing it right and
they start to see you doing it right and
all of a sudden you switch and start
going over there you know that you know
that this ain't nothing son is Pagan you
know that the gospel is Pagan but
somebody that might be following you and
you might being watching you and you an
example to them then what's going to
happen they are going to because they
don't have the knowledge and
understanding you have they going to
start dealing with this Pagan God and if
you have children then the children
going to be confused they not going to
know what to
believe like your brother said stand
strong that's all I have to say that's
that 10th verse you're referring to in
the same chapter guest caller that's
that 10th
verse read it Tel man see thee which at
verse
n but take heed lest by any means this
Liberty of yours become a stumbling
block to them that are
weak any man see thee which have
knowledge sit at me in the idols Temple
shall not the conscience of him which is
in weat be embolden to eat those things
which I offer to
Idols verse 11 but through th knowledge
shall the weak brother perish for whom
Christ died that's what the guest call
is
saying so the whole thing is you just
can't think about
me cuz you don't know who is watching
you who else in the family is looking at
you might be getting ready uh to cross
over might take them 10 or 15 years but
all of a sudden you switch and start
going in another Direction you know it
ain't nothing but they don't have your
knowledge and they don't have your
strength so what you going to do is you
going to get them cut
off because of they too weak to
discern what God are they
serving this what this is saying just
food for thought that's all I have to
say yeah all right hope that aned your
question there uh sister Deborah time
check yes the time is
9:03 9 4 now 904 all right we'd like to
thank everybody from all around the
world who sent in all those questions we
thank you and we took joy in answering
them along with you but we'd like to say
that if you submitted a question and we
didn't get to it this evening it is
because we ran out of time but we will
ask sister Deborah to take it put it in
rotation and we will address that
question next week so please don't
resubmit your question and thank you all
for joining us and we like to say until
we all come together again be safe out
there be blessed stay prayed up and may
the Lord have mercy on us all as brother
tanzel closes us out Our Father which
art in Heaven hallow be thy name thy
kingdom come thy will be done in earth
as it is in heaven give us this day our
daily bread and forgive us of our debts
as we forgive our debt to us and lead us
not into temptation but Deliver Us from
Evil
for thine is the kingdom and the power
and the glory forever in Jesus name we
pray amen amen